<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vectorr Mapping</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_full_text">Full Text Directions</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Vectorr Mobile: Instructions for Use\n\n"
"Mapping Software Quick-Start Guide\n"
"1. Launch the Vectorr Mapping program.\n"
"2. Select the starting building and room from the dropdown menus.\n"
"        a) This represents the beginning location of all directions generated.\n"
"        b) If preferred, a search tool is also provided which will find points with names related to the one given.\n"
"3. Select the destination building and room from the dropdown menus.\n"
"        a) These destination attributes are the place to which you would like directions.\n"
"        b) The same search tool is provided for destinations.\n"
"4. Press the button labelled “Directions” to generate a route between the two locations.\n"
"        a) Text directions, along with a traced route on a map will appear if the program was able to find a route between the two points. \n"
"                i) If Vectorr Mapping is unable to find a route, it will print out: “No Valid Route.” \n"
"        b) Stepping through the route is as easy as pressing the next button to advance to the next step in the route. \n"
"        c) Remembering past directions is easy too, just hit the previous button.\n"
"        d) Pressing the “Full Text Directions” button will allow viewing of all the text directions in order.\n"
"                i) Vectorr Mapping will also provide a time estimate for the route when viewing full text directions.\n"
"5. To generate directions along the reverse of the route, simply press the “Swap” button to return to the original location.\n\n\n"
"Setting Preferences for Routing\n\n"
"Vectorr Mapping includes options for preferences to be set to change the route generated based on a user’s choices.\n"
"1) Before generating any directions, select the button in the top right corner to change preferences.\n"
"2) From the page that appears, a user can choose:\n"
"        The color scheme of the program (including a color-blind accessibility mode).\n"
"        The likelihood of the program generating a route that uses stairs. \n"
"        The likelihood of the program generating a route that goes outside.\n"
"        How long it will take to travel the route.\n"
"3) Simply press the “Back” button on the mobile device to return to the main mapping page.\n"

    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
</resources>
